威尔 · 森塔斯: 其中一个奖金我想给你之前，因为我说我们移动
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: One of the bonuses I
want to give you before as I say we moved
第三个解决方案。
to solution three.
这将是下一个大美化和
Which is gonna be the big
next prettifying and
简化所有这些对象创建。
simplifying of all this object creation.
还有一件额外的东西我想给你们，那就是这个。
One more bonus thing I want
to give you which is this.
在方法增量中声明和调用一个新函数。
Declaring and calling a new function
inside our method increment.
让我把我们添加的东西清理一下，这样我们就不会搞混了。
Let me just clear away the stuff we
added there so we don't get confused.
让我们把这些额外的零件处理掉吧。
Let's just get rid of
these bonus pieces here.
在底部你可以看到，我调用了递增函数,
So at the bottom there you can see,
I'm calling the increment function,
和以前一样，这是同样的密码。
as before, this is the same code.
我在这里唯一改变的就是,
The only thing I've changed here, folk,
我已经将 increment 方法作为用户函数存储中的唯一方法。
is I've put the increment method as the
only method in the user function store.
我刚刚在行上定义了它，所以我们可以在这里添加一些额外的东西。
And I've just defined it over lines, so
that we can add something extra in there.
是这样吗，我真的这么做了吗？
Is that right,
is that actually what I've done?
我希望如此，我认为这是正确的，希望如此。
I hope it is,
I think it is right hopefully.
现在我们在这里只有增量函数。
So now we only have our
increment function in here.
但这只是为了简单起见，所以我们可以在其中做一些事情,
But that's just for simplicity's sake,
so we can do something inside of it,
好了。
there we go.
威尔 · 森特斯: 约翰不喜欢我把黑板擦掉。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: John's not liking
my bad erasing of the board.
好的，这是我们在 user1上调用的增量方法,
Okay, there's our increment
method being called on user1,
通过原始连接，没问题吧？
via the proto link, yep, all good?
它能做到这一点？
It does this.score++?
我现在把它稍稍展开因为我想这么做,
I just put it now on to slightly spread
it out because I want to do this,
我想在增量方法里面。
I want to inside of the increment method.
因为如果你开始用这种风格写代码,
Because if you start thinking
in this style of writing code,
你会发现自己一直在使用递增方法。
you'll find yourself all the time,
having to, in that increment method.
一堆代码，大概10行，12行，还有
A bunch of code maybe 10 lines,
12 lines, and
你可能不希望只有12行[声音]。
you may not want to have
that just 12 lines [SOUND].
您可能需要将其分解为增量内部的小函数
You may wanna break that into little
mini-functions inside of the increment
方法，只有一行，它可能是12行。
methods, only one line,
it may be 12 lines.
你想要定义它们的内部,
And you wanna define inside of them,
有些函数甚至可能在 increment 中运行。
some functions that you may even
end up running inside of increment.
你可能还是想用 user1。
Which you're probably gonna
still wanna use user1.
这将创造出一些有趣而有趣的挑战，让我们来看看。
That's gonna create some interesting and
intriguing challenges, let's have a look.
我要保持这个超级简单
I'm gonna keep this super simple and
我们只需要在函数中结束这个.score + + 。
we're literally just going to wrap
up the this.score++ in a function.
然后当场运行这个函数。
And then run that function right there and
then.
因为我想表达我的观点但结果是一样的,
Because I wanna make a point, but
it's gonna be exactly the same,
看看这个。
have a look at that.
我把它放在.score + + ，看一下，在一个函数里面，我在这里调用它。
I put this.score++, take a look, inside
of a function I'm calling it right there.
把它放进去，加1，我就在这里称它为1。
Put it inside, add 1, and
I'm calling it right there.
很明显，在实践中我从来没有真正做到这一点，但我想说明一点。
Obviously I'd never really do this in
practice, but I wanna make a point.
但实际上，我们经常创造一些小功能
But in reality we're often
creating little functions
在我们的对象上调用的方法中。
inside of our method that's
being called on our object.
这将会非常有趣。
And this is going to be
really interesting here.
让我们回到我们的底线 user1.increment,
So let's get back to our bottom
line here user1.increment,
让我们调用 user1.increment。
let's call user1.increment.
显然没有什么变化。
Apparently not much has changed.
我把 this.score + + 加入到这里的一个小 baby 函数中,
I've just put my this.score++ into
a little baby function inside of here,
我会立刻参选。
that I'm gonna immediately run.
各位，这些都是额外的东西，我想带你们参观一下这个生态系统
And, people, these are just bonus things
I wanna show you around the ecosystem of
原型世界和这个关键词。
the prototype world and the this keyword.
那么，让我们来运行 user1.increment，Braden，全新的？
So there we go, let's run our
user1.increment, Braden, brand new?
布莱登: 执行环境。
&gt;&gt; Braden: Execution context.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 执行上下文，没错，就是这样，我们进入它。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context,
exactly, there it is, into it we go.
首先，Braden，在本地记忆中，我们的隐含参数是什么？
First thing, Braden, in local memory,
what's our implicit parameter immediately?
这个，是的，分配什么？
This, yeah, assigned what?
用户1，不管剩下什么，这很好,
User1 whatever's left, so that's good,
因为你想在 user1上做一些代码，然后改变分数，即 user1。
because you wanna do some code on
user1 and change the score, the user1.
在增量核心里面我们接下来要做什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What's the next thing
we do inside of the increment core?
布莱登: 声明一个函数 add1。
&gt;&gt; Braden: Declare a function add1.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 好极了，add1，就是这个，函数 add1。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent,
add1, there it is, function add1.
那我们现在该怎么办，布莱登？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What do we
do then immediately, Braden?
布莱登: 运行这个函数。
&gt;&gt; Braden: Run the function.
我们调用函数，运行函数，调用函数,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We call the function, we
run the function, we invoke the function,
都是同一个意思。
they all mean the same thing.
全新的什么，布莱登？
Brand new what, Braden?
布莱登: 执行环境。
&gt;&gt; Braden: Execution context.
执行上下文，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context,
exactly.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 现在事情变得有趣了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Now
things get interesting.
威尔 · 森特斯: 里面的代码行是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What's
the line of code inside?
布莱登: 这个——威尔 · 森特斯: 嗯，代码行——
&gt;&gt; Braden: This-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well, the line of code-
布莱登: 代码行应该是
&gt;&gt; Braden: The line of code would be
这个，得分 + + 。
this.score++.
威尔 · 斯坦斯: 这个，得分。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: This.score.
2. Will Sentance: + + .
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: ++.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们在阿迪本地内存中的价值是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What [LAUGH] is our
value of this inside add1's local memory?
大概是 user1，因为我们在这个函数里面，我们怎么想,
Presumably it's user1 cuz we are inside
this function, what do we think,
所有人？
everybody?
这是有道理的，其他语言都是这样做的！
That makes sense,
every other language does that!
什么，布莱登，你觉得是这样吗？
What, Braden, do you think it's that?
布莱登: 没有。
&gt;&gt; Braden: No.
威尔 · 森特斯: 不，(笑) ，荣耀！
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No, [LAUGH], glories!
布莱登: (笑)威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，所以这是
&gt;&gt; Braden: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes, so this is one of
这些可能不是最好的早期 JavaScript 实现。
those arguably, maybe not the best
earlier implementations of JavaScript.
尤其是在其他语言中，当你在使用一种语言的时候，它是绝对标准的
Especially as in other languages it's
absolutely standard that while you're
在方法里面。
inside the method.
相关对象，我们关心的用数据做事情的对象。
The pertinent object, the object that we
care about doing stuff to with the data.
是贯穿始终的，将是我们运行方法的对象。
Is throughout, going to be the object
that we're running the method on.
即使我们在内部声明其他函数并运行它们,
Even if we declare other
functions inside and run them,
他们在当地的记忆中就是这样。
they're this in their local memory.
但是不，这个在当地的记忆里，布拉登,
But no, the this in the local memory here,
Braden,
你想猜猜它指的是什么吗？
you wanna take a guess what it refers to?
[声音]威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们的缺省值是什么
&gt;&gt; [SOUND]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What's our default for
这个？
the this?
怎么了，丹？
Yeah, Dan?
全局记忆。
&gt;&gt; Dan: The global memory.
嗯，全局窗口对象,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well,
the global window object,
特别是现在没用。
especially not useful at this moment.
所以我们最终会连接到这个有趣的全局对象，窗口,
And so we'd end up attaching to this
funny global object called window,
一笔财产，一笔生意。
a property on it, a score.
那么默认情况下就不能定义了，我们会尝试增加它。
Which would then be undefined by default,
and we'd try and increment it.
真漂亮，那是一只漂亮的虫子。
[SOUND] beautiful, well,
that's one of those glorious bugs.
不是虫子只是如果我们知道它是怎么工作的,
Not a bug, it's just like,
I guess if we know how it's working,
这是不可能的。
it's not gonna happen.
所以在过去，这是如何处理的，这是一个有趣的方式。
So in the old days, how was this
dealt with, it was a funny way.
丹: (笑)威尔 · 森坦斯: 他们过去常常,
&gt;&gt; Dan: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: They used to,
各位，你们知道这个吗？
do you know this, everybody?
他们过去常常这样，他们过去常常那样,
They used to do this,
they used to do that,
他们以前经常这么做。
they used to do that=this.
这样就等于这个 user1，漂亮。
Which would set that equal to this user1,
beautiful.
然后在这里面，我们不会写这个.score + + ，我们会怎么做？
And then inside of here, we wouldn't
write this.score ++, what would we do?
阿丹: 那个。
&gt;&gt; Dan: That.
威尔 · 森特斯: That.score + + ，我们会在本地内存中寻找它，它不在那里。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That.score ++, we'd look
for that in local memory, it ain't there.
所以我们在这里抓取 user1，没问题[声音]没问题。
So we go out here and grab user1,
no problem [SOUND] no problem.
您可以在整个代码中看到这些函数中的许多内容。
You'd see that=this inside many of
these functions throughout the code.
这不是最漂亮的设计路线，我得说。
It wasn't the most beautiful design path,
and I've gotta say.
还有其他的方法,
There are other ways of doing it,
你可以运行 add1函数，我们把父母放在最后。
you can actually run the add1 function,
we're putting parents on the end.
但是也有一些手动的方法来运行这个函数,
But also, there's some manual
ways to run the function,
有人知道手动操作吗 Kayla？
does anyone know the manual ways,
yeah, Kayla?
打电话或者回复。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Call or reply.
威尔 · 森特斯: 打电话或者回复，或者捆绑，完全正确，好吧,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Call or
reply, or bind, exactly, well,
宾德要做一件非常接近的事。
bind is gonna do something very close.
电话和答复，我们要进入这个更多的公关部分。
Call and reply, we're gonna go
into this more in the PR parts.
如果你想去看深海潜水，我们有什么，你可以去。
If you wanna go watch that,
the deep dive, what we have, you can.
但是很快就会变得很酷,
But just quickly add1.cool, actually,
也许我现在就可以展示给你看，add1。
I probably might as well
show you right now, add1.
顺便说一句，这是很标准的，这个东西，太神奇了。
Let's get rid of, by the way that was very
standard that that.this thing, amazing.
我不认为这本身就很糟糕，我知道这很愚蠢。
I don't think it was inherently terrible,
it's kind of know it's pretty dumb.
但是还有另一种方式，就像我说的运行广告的一个功能。
But there is another way as I say
of running the ad one function.
手动，我们实际上得到控制什么这个任务
Manually where we actually get to take
control of what the this assignment
就在里面。
is inside of it.
这有点酷，这是通过运行它使用凉爽或申请。
That's kinda cool, and that is by
running it using the cool or apply.
对于这一点，他们都做了同样的事情。
For this bit, they both do the same thing.
如果我经过这里，这里，那么不管我经过什么,
And if I've passed in here,
this, then whatever I pass in,
这将评估为什么，各位？
the this will evaluate to what, everybody?
用户1。
&gt;&gt; Braden: User1.
Will Sentance: User1，因此 this inside of here 将被设置为 that-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: User1, and therefore the
this inside of here will be set to that-
用户1。
&gt;&gt; Braden: User1.
用户1，然后它再次工作。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: User1,
and then it works again.